

Tran Thi Lien

FRESHER TEST ENGINEER

CONTACT -

- 038 993 7574
- 🔽 tranthilien.m@gmail.com
- 26/04/1990
- FPT Plaza1 Building Da Nang
- 1 https://lientran1990.github.io/

SKILLS -

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Good in Excel
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScrip
- React
- Cit
- Manual & Automation Test
- Java

SOFT SKILLS

- Wellingness to learn
- Hard-working
- Time management
- Commitment to excellence and self-improvement
- Intermediate level in English

CARFER GOALS

On the way to become Woman In Tech. I will try to learn new things, hardworking to be able to participate and contribute to many projects. Now I'm just a fresher with little knowledge and experience. My career goal is in about 3 years, I will be an experienced Front-end Developer.

EDUCATION —

META FRONT-END DEVELOPER

07/2023 - now

Coursera

https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/11VfbwqFTrsZ_vppccr1TlKCI68x4M3-q

SOFTWARE TESTER SPECIALIZATION

09/2022 - 06/2023

Funix

https://drive.google.com/file/d/10U1frHVBsDl27hBJZ-3ngpJgiSMEGTlS/view

ACCOUNTING

09/2009 - 06/2013

Da Nang University of Economics

PROJECTS - ASSIGMENTS -

1 - Portfolio Resume

Resume is a resume and CV theme for Bootstrap created by Start Bootstrap. It's reffered from the site:

 $https:/\!/github.com/StartBootstrap/startbootstrap-resume.$

- <u>Link</u>: https://lientran1990.github.io/

2 - Project: My-first-webpage

This is an webpage with the structure of using basic html and css. Header contain the logo and the main content contain a promotional banner with three columns. The footer will have two columns: the first column have a small logo and the second one have copywriting.

-Link: https://lientran1990.github.io/My-first-webpage/

3 - Project: Tester

A project including manual and automation testing. Write test cases and test website functionality based on SRS. Create Maven project, install libraries. Write code, execute test cases with TestNG, export reports with ReportNG.

· Link: https://github.com/lientran1990/MyProjects

EXPERIENCE -

ACCOUNTS PAYABLE

02/2020 - 02/2021

American International Hospital

Keeping track of all payments and expenditures. Maintaining historical records. Paying vendors by scheduling pay checks.

GENERAL ACCOUNTANT

05/2014 - 05/2019

Tam Tri Hospital

Reviewing all financial transactions. Preparing financial statements, tax returns, and other reports based on standard accounting practices. © topcv.vn

